This summer, the UK, and much of the northern hemisphere, has experienced a heatwave – a sustained period of roasting temperatures and scorching sunshine.
今年夏天，英国及北半球大部分地区都经历了一场热浪——一段持续的高温和烈日炙烤的时期。
While many welcome the Sun and warmth, too much can be dangerous to health.
尽管许多人欢迎阳光和温暖，但过度暴晒对健康有害。
So what are the best ways to keep cool?
那么，保持凉爽的最佳方法是什么呢？
Firstly, avoiding exposure is a good idea, says the UK Met office.
英国气象局表示，首先，避免暴晒是个好主意。
This means not going out in direct sunlight, or, where possible, sticking to shadows and shade.
这意味着不要在阳光直射下外出，或者尽可能待在阴影和阴凉处。
This also means that covering up is a good idea.
这也意味着做好防晒很重要。
Wear loose, airy clothing, which fully covers the body, as well as a hat and sunglasses.
穿上宽松透气、能完全遮盖身体的衣物，同时戴上帽子和太阳镜。
In addition, a parasol could provide valuable protection.
此外，阳伞可以提供有效的防护。
Finally, the UK's National Health Service recommends not going out between 11 in the morning and three in the afternoon if you are vulnerable to the Sun.
最后，英国国家医疗服务体系建议，如果你容易被太阳晒伤，避免在上午11点到下午3点之间外出。
Staying hydrated is another excellent idea.
保持水分充足是另一个好方法。
The human body is approximately 60% water, which on a hot day, can be depleted through sweat.
人体约60%是水分，在炎热的天气里，水分会通过汗水流失。
If this water is not replenished, dehydration can occur.
如果不补充水分，就会脱水。
The US Geological Survey's water science school recommends drinking three litres a day for an adult male, and 2.3 litres for an adult female, though this varies according to circumstance.
美国地质调查局水科学学校建议，成年男性每天饮用3升水，成年女性饮用2.3升水，尽管这会因情况而异。
You should also avoid alcohol, which dehydrates the body.
你还应该避免饮酒，因为酒精会让身体脱水。
Whether at home or at work, steps should be taken to reduce temperatures indoors, too.
无论是在家还是在工作中，都应该采取措施降低室内温度。
Blinds, curtains and shades should be closed and windows opened to allow the building to ventilate.
关闭百叶窗、窗帘和遮阳帘，并打开窗户让房间通风。
This is especially important at night while you sleep.
这在夜间睡觉时尤为重要。
The UK Met office says "night cooling is important as it allows the body to recuperate."
英国气象局表示：“夜间降温很重要，因为它能让身体恢复。”
Finally, for those working outside, extra precautions should be taken.
最后，对于那些在户外工作的人，需要采取额外的预防措施。
In addition to staying covered and drinking water, high-factor sunscreen should be worn to stop sunburn and the possible development of skin cancer.
除了做好防晒和补充水分外，还应涂抹高倍数防晒霜，以防止晒伤和可能引发的皮肤癌。
In addition, those who perform physical tasks in the Sun should be careful of heatstroke, which, according to the UK Met Office, can be fatal.
此外，在阳光下从事体力劳动的人应注意中暑——据英国气象局称，中暑可能会致命。
For many, summer is a well-loved period of warmth and outdoor activity, but as the old saying goes, everything in moderation.
对许多人来说，夏天是备受喜爱的温暖和户外活动的季节，但正如老话所说，凡事都要适度。
That said, as long as people remember the basics and look after themselves, there is no reason why a prolonged heatwave can't become the summer that everyone remembers.
尽管如此，只要人们记住基本常识并照顾好自己，一场持续的热浪未必不能成为每个人都难忘的夏天。